[
  {
    "question": "somerset myoma partschinite exorcism potamic aerobically pritch",
    "answers": [
      "chob",
      "benthicB",
      "contumacity elytrigerous"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "reproposal overview theatricalize Bucconidae semiamplexicaul aba",
    "answers": [
      "domiciliar",
      "limewaterB",
      "tirrivee shipbreaking",
      "spininess Heracleopolitan"
    ],
    "scores": [ 1, 0, 0, 0 ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "supereffluence snipefish ultragood cylindroid microzoospore alloxuremi",
    "answers": [
      "undischarged",
      "WandoroboB",
      "bygane unweelness",
      "kish fungo"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1, 0 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "unreelable vestmented pseudonymousness folial caprifoliaceous Tricia sulphoantimo",
    "answers": [
      "mesosaur",
      "increasableB",
      "anamorphose olease",
      "ecdemite cramp"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 1, 0, 0 ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "glucase inventively phytosterin want inosculation denticate halcyoni",
    "answers": [
      "stoichiometrical",
      "journeymanB",
      "thirteenfold mesatipellic",
      "oriform behoove"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1, 0 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "cobaea paramountcy Ulsterian decemflorous Chytroi hermitically p",
    "answers": [
      "unliveableness",
      "rabbaniteB",
      "Bucky Microrhopias",
      "submaxillary indigeneity"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1, 0 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "wheenge metacresol climate Xanthian undershine her",
    "answers": [
      "undecylic",
      "mesotrochB",
      "corrosiveness billboard",
      "staw jerkily"
    ],
    "scores": [ 1, 0, 0, 0 ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "city subcavity jugful lousewort intertropic undervalue matril",
    "answers": [
      "shattery",
      "daringB",
      "bulblet undangerous",
      "kamikaze kerseymere"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1, 0 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "microphotometer handwrite insinuating cable arkosic redecussate s",
    "answers": [
      "ankerite",
      "propoundB",
      "it brutishness",
      "feldsparphyre jink"
    ],
    "scores": [ 0, 0, 1, 0 ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "soddenly superphlogistication overhatted enteroanastomosis hyperpiesis agential marly feverishly",
    "answers": [
      "haikal",
      "allusionB",
      "monopersulphuric preadvisable",
      "Malaccan travated"
    ],
    "scores": [ 1, 0, 0, 0 ],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
